<add>
	<doc>
		<field name="id" boost="1.0">0</field>
		<field name="release" boost="1.0">2005</field>
		<field name="title" boost="4.0">Amudhey</field>
		<field name="origin" boost="1.0">Tamil</field>
		<field name="director" boost="1.0">Ezhil</field>
		<field name="cast" boost="1.0">Jai Akash, Madhumitha, Pranathi</field>
		<field name="genre" boost="1.0">romance</field>
		<field name="wikipage" boost="1.0">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Amudhey</field>
		<field name="plot" boost="2.0">Dhinakar (Jai Akash) hailing from an ordinary middle-class family and Nancy, a software engineer and sole breadwinner for her family, are neighbors in love with each other. But their dreams of getting married are shattered when their self-centered parents decide on proposals of their own choice.
Notwithstanding the overbearing parental pressures, Nancy marries Victor, a multimillionaire businessman, while Dhinakar marries his cousin - but not before the lead pair enter into a sly pact.
Dhinakar and Nancy contrive to marry the spouses chosen by their parents, only to officially dissolve their unhappy unions later and thereby pave way to their union. After a sequence of events, Nancy successfully convinces Victor about her unreserved enthusiasm for her past love. Nancy gets her divorce and takes the first step towards making a fresh start, but events overtake her in an unexpected final act.
</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id" boost="1.0">1</field>
		<field name="release" boost="1.0">2001</field>
		<field name="title" boost="4.0">The Cat's Meow</field>
		<field name="origin" boost="1.0">American</field>
		<field name="director" boost="1.0">Peter Bogdanovich</field>
		<field name="cast" boost="1.0">Kirsten Dunst, Edward Herrmann, Eddie Izzard, Cary Elwes, Joanna Lumley, Jennifer Tilly</field>
		<field name="genre" boost="1.0">drama</field>
		<field name="wikipage" boost="1.0">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Cat%27s_Meow</field>
		<field name="plot" boost="2.0">November 15, 1924: Among those boarding the luxury yacht Oneida in San Pedro, California are its owner, publishing magnate William Randolph Hearst, and his mistress, silent film star Marion Davies; motion picture mogul Thomas H. Ince, whose birthday is the reason for the weekend cruise, and his mistress, starlet Margaret Livingston; international film star Charlie Chaplin; English writer Elinor Glyn; and Louella Parsons, a film critic for Hearst's New York American.
Several of those participating in the weekend's festivities are at a crossroads in their lives and/or careers. Chaplin, still dealing with the critical and commercial failure of A Woman of Paris and rumors he has impregnated 16-year-old Lita Grey (who appeared in his film The Kid) is in the midst of preparing The Gold Rush. Davies longs to appear in a slapstick comedy rather than the somber costume dramas to which Hearst has kept her confined. Ince's eponymous film studio is in dire financial straits, so he hopes to convince Hearst to take him on as a partner in Cosmopolitan Pictures. Parsons would like to relocate from the East Coast to more glamorous Hollywood.
Hearst suspects Davies and Chaplin have engaged in an affair, a suspicion shared by Ince, who seeks proof he can present to Hearst in order to curry favor with him. In the wastepaper basket in Chaplin's stateroom, Ince discovers a discarded love letter to Davies and pockets it with plans to produce it at an opportune moment. When he finally does, Hearst is enraged. His anger is fueled further when he finds a brooch he had given Davies in Chaplin's cabin. Hearst concludes it was lost there during a romantic liaison, and he rifles Marion's room for further evidence.
Armed with a pistol, Hearst searches the yacht for Chaplin in the middle of the night. Ince, meanwhile, runs into Davies and the two sit and talk with Ince donning a hat Chaplin had worn. Davies explains to Ince her love for Hearst and her regret at an earlier affair with Chaplin. She states "I never loved him" just as Hearst arrives behind them. Thinking Davies is referring to him, and mistaking Ince for Chaplin, a jealous Hearst shoots Ince. The assault is witnessed by Parsons, who had heard noises and went to investigate.
Hearst arranges to dock in San Diego and have a waiting ambulance take the dying Ince home. He phones the injured man's wife and tells her Ince attempted suicide when Livingston tried to end their affair, assuring her the truth won't reach the media. To the rest of his guests he announces Ince's ulcer flared up and required immediate medical attention. Davies, of course, knows the truth, and confides in Chaplin. Also armed with that knowledge is Parsons, who assures Hearst his secret will be safe in exchange for a lifetime contract with the Hearst Corporation, thus laying the groundwork for her lengthy career as one of Hollywood's most powerful gossip columnists.
After seeing Ince off, Hearst confronts Davies and Chaplin. He is berated by Chaplin, who expects Davies to join him. Hearst, however, challenges Chaplin to guarantee Davies that he can promise her a happy life. When Chaplin fails to answer, Hearst informs Chaplin of the vow of silence he and the fellow guests have made to keep the weekend's activities a secret. Chaplin despairs as he realizes the murder has strengthened Davies' love for Hearst.
The film concludes with the guests leaving Ince's funeral, as Glyn relates what became of them:
Tom Ince was largely forgotten after the events of his death. Very few newspapers reported it, no police action was taken, and of all the people on board only one was ever questioned. It is concluded that in Hollywood, "the place just off the coast of the planet Earth," no two accounts of the story are the same.</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id" boost="1.0">2</field>
		<field name="release" boost="1.0">2002</field>
		<field name="title" boost="4.0">Like Mike</field>
		<field name="origin" boost="1.0">American</field>
		<field name="director" boost="1.0">John Schultz</field>
		<field name="cast" boost="1.0">Bow Wow, Morris Chestnut, Jonathan Lipnicki</field>
		<field name="genre" boost="1.0">comedy</field>
		<field name="wikipage" boost="1.0">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Like_Mike</field>
		<field name="plot" boost="2.0">Calvin Cambridge and his two best friends, Murph and Reg Stevens, live in an orphanage. Murph is the youngest of the trio, and has a very close bond with Calvin. At night they all have to sell chocolate for the awkward orphanage director, Stan Bittleman, after each home game of the (fictional) NBA team, the Los Angeles Knights.
Calvin meets the team's coach, who is impressed by Calvin's knowledge of basketball and honesty about the chocolates and offers Calvin tickets for the next game. Inside a thrift store donation box, Calvin finds a pair of old sneakers that were used by Michael Jordan. Calvin's sneakers are taken by a jealous bully named Ox who throws them onto an overhead power line. When Calvin tries to retrieve them that night in a rainstorm he is shocked by a lightning bolt.
Calvin and his friends attend the basketball game between the Knights and the Minnesota Timberwolves. After the second quarter ends, the team's star player, Tracy Reynolds, prepares for a halftime contest. Calvin's ticket number is called and he goes one on one with Tracy. Calvin ends the contest with a dunk after bouncing the ball off the backboard. Murph, Reg, and the surprised crowd give Calvin a standing ovation. Calvin is signed to a one-day contract by the Knights. Calvin prepares for his first game with the Knights, but realizes that he is not there to play. When the Knights play the San Antonio Spurs they start losing badly and Coach Wagner decides to let Calvin play in the fourth quarter. Calvin leads a comeback against the Spurs and they win, which leads to Calvin getting a season contract. Reynolds becomes his mentor since Calvin is a minor. Calvin brings teamwork to the Knights and makes them one of the best teams in the league. Tracy starts to respect Calvin after Calvin gets himself into trouble when making sure that Tracy didn't miss curfew.
Bittleman signs a contract with the team that all of Calvin's money will go to him until Calvin is eighteen or adopted. When the second option is about to become true, Bittleman grows desperate and steals Calvin's shoes and bets US$100,000 against the Knights.
After convincing Ox and his cohorts that Bittleman is selfish, Ox takes the shoes out of Bittleman's safe. The kids head to the arena with Calvin's sneakers. Bittleman escapes and sends goons after Calvin in a failed attempt to steal the shoes back. Calvin makes it to the arena with the shoes after the 3rd quarter ends with Vince Carter and the Toronto Raptors routing the Knights 80–59.
In the 4th quarter of the last regular season, Calvin is put into the game by the coach and the Knights start to make a comeback. After a pile-on towards the end of the game, Calvin's shoes are ruined with the Knights down by one point. Without the shoes and wanting to be a normal child, Calvin sadly tells the team this will be his last game. In the final play, Calvin manages to pump fake to get Vince Carter to jump and pass the ball to Tracy. Tracy makes the game-winning shot to clinch the Knights their first playoff appearance. After the game, Calvin bids poignant goodbyes to Tracy and Coach Wagner.
After going back to his orphanage, Calvin is surprised by Tracy's return and intentions to adopt him. Calvin agrees under the condition that he also adopts Murph (whom Tracy previously met and bonded with), not wanting to leave him behind. Reg is later adopted by a different family, though they all still keep in touch. Bittleman is missing because he doesn't have enough money to pay the bet and the orphanage is now sponsored by the Knights.</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id" boost="1.0">3</field>
		<field name="release" boost="1.0">2004</field>
		<field name="title" boost="4.0">The Phantom of the Opera</field>
		<field name="origin" boost="1.0">American</field>
		<field name="director" boost="1.0">Joel Schumacher</field>
		<field name="cast" boost="1.0">Gerard Butler, Emmy Rossum, Patrick Wilson</field>
		<field name="genre" boost="1.0">musical</field>
		<field name="wikipage" boost="1.0">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Phantom_of_the_Opera_(2004_film)</field>
		<field name="plot" boost="2.0">In 1919, the Opéra Populaire holds a public auction to clear the theatre's vaults. Raoul, Viscount de Chagny purchases a papier-mâché music box in the shape of a monkey and eyes it sadly as Madame Giry, an aged woman dressed in black, inspects him. The auctioneer then presents a shattered chandelier as the next item up for bid, claiming that it once played a key role in "the strange affair of the Phantom of the Opera". As it flickers to life and slowly ascends to its original place in the rafters, the auction is transported back in time to the year 1870.
Back to this time, while the company rehearses for a performance of the grand opera Hannibal, manager Monsieur Lefèvre announces that he has decided to retire and that the opera has been purchased by Richard Firmin and Gilles André, two men who have no experience with the arts whatsoever. When resident soprano Carlotta Giudicelli begins to sing for the managers, a backdrop collapses and causes everyone to blame the "Opera Ghost", a mysterious figure who is rumored to live in the catacombs beneath the theater. Carlotta refuses to sing and storms offstage, leaving Firmin and André no choice but to cancel the performance. At the last minute, ballet mistress Madame Giry suggests that dancer Christine Daaé take Carlotta's place as she has been "well taught." The managers reluctantly agree and, to their surprise, Christine wins them over.
Later that night, after Christine's triumphant stage debut, she explains to Madame Giry's daughter, Meg, that she is being coached by a mysterious tutor who she refers to as the "Angel of Music"; a tutor who her late father said would teach her to sing. Christine returns to her dressing room to find Raoul, the opera's new patron and her former childhood sweetheart, waiting for her. The two reminisce about their youth as Christine tells Raoul her secret, only for him to laugh at her "fantasy" and invite her to dinner despite her protests. Unbeknownst to everyone, except Madame Giry, the Phantom of the Opera locks Christine in her dressing room and reveals himself in her mirror to her before hypnotizing her and taking her to his subterranean lair.
The Phantom reveals to her that he loves her and wants her to love him back. He shows Christine a bust of herself, wearing a wedding dress and veil, causing her to faint, and the Phantom places her in a bed. The next morning she awakes to find the Phantom writing music. She approaches him and removes his mask out of curiosity. He bursts into a fit of rage, covering his face with his hand. He at first says she must stay forever because she saw his deformities, revealing that he "dreams of beauty". Pitying him Christine hands him back his mask and the two have a moment of understanding. He then decides to return her to the opera house.
That morning, the two managers lament Christine's disappearance, as well as series of notes they received from the Opera Ghost trying to blackmail them for his payment and ordering them on how to run the opera house. When Carlotta returns, she is furious to find a note sent to her saying if she sang as the countess in Il Muto that night instead of Christine, then disaster "beyond [their] imagination" would occur. Firmin and André ignore the ghost's warnings and give Carlotta the lead role. That night, the Phantom interrupts the performance and criticizes their failure to follow his orders.
Carlotta continues to sing, but her voice croaks (as a result of the Phantom tampering with her throat spray) and the lead role is given to Christine. While the ballet is being performed, the Phantom, not realizing the performance change, encounters the chief stagehand Joseph Buquet and strangles him before hanging him from above, creating chaos. Christine flees to the roof with Raoul. She reveals to him that she has seen the Phantom's face and fears him, but also pities him because of his sadness. Raoul tells Christine he loves her and will protect her forevermore. Christine returns his love, kissing him passionately and they both leave the roof. The Phantom, who witnessed the scene, becomes heartbroken. He then hears them both singing together. Growing furious at Raoul, he vows revenge on them both.
Three months later, a masquerade party ensues in the opera house. At the party, Christine wears her new engagement ring from Raoul. The event is interrupted once again by the Phantom, who is dressed as Red Death. The Phantom brings his own composition, Don Juan Triumphant, and orders the managers to stage the opera. Raoul exits the room and Christine approaches the Phantom. At the sight of the engagement ring, the Phantom rips it from Christine and disappears into a trap on the floor. Raoul tries to follow him but is stopped by Madame Giry, who privately tells him the story of the Phantom's past. When she was a little girl, she went to a freak circus where they featured a deformed child in a cage. The child was beaten while everyone watched and laughed. The ringmaster then removed a burlap sack covering the child's face, revealing his deformity. Only the young Madame Giry pitied him. She was the last to leave and saw the child strangle the ringmaster with a rope. Chased by the police, Madame Giry helped him escape and found shelter for him beneath the opera house, where she has hidden him from the world ever since.
Christine takes a carriage to visit her father's grave, but the Phantom secretly takes over the reins. Raoul follows when he realizes she's gone. Christine arrives and laments over her father's death. The Phantom tries to win her back by pretending to be her father's angel, but Raoul arrives and stops him. A sword fight ensues in the cemetery, where Raoul eventually disarms the Phantom and is about to kill him, but Christine pleads for him not to. His rage seemingly augmented, the Phantom watches angrily as Christine and Raoul ride away.
Christine admits she is afraid of the Phantom and tells Raoul he will never stop trying to recapture her. Raoul realizes that they can use the Phantom's opera to capture him, as he will surely attend. Don Juan Triumphant is performed, and the Phantom makes his entrance (having secretly replaced the lead) with Christine. Raoul can do nothing but watch from his box as Christine falls for the Phantom yet again. However, she once again removes his mask, revealing his deformities to the entire audience, who scream in fear. He escapes with her by dropping the chandelier and setting the opera house on fire. An angry mob gathers in the opera house to hunt him.
The Phantom brings Christine back down to his lair. Madame Giry shows Raoul where the Phantom lives hopeful he can beat the mob and rescue Christine safely. The Phantom forces her to don the wedding dress and once again professes his love, and orders Christine to marry him. Christine tries to convince the Phantom that she does not fear his ugliness, but rather his anger and willingness to kill to get what he wants. Just then, Raoul enters the lair, and the Phantom ties him to a gate and threatens to kill him if Christine refuses to marry him. Christine reflects over the impossible choice before passionately kissing the Phantom to show him he is not alone in the world. The Phantom is shocked from experiencing real human love for the first time in his life. Ashamed of his murderous actions, and hearing the echo of the angry mob approaching his lair, he tells Christine and Raoul to immediately leave and orders them to never return. He finds comfort in a little monkey music box. Christine approaches the Phantom, who tells her that he loves her, and she silently gives him the diamond ring from her finger to remember her by. After Christine and Raoul leave, the Phantom smashes every mirror in his underground lair and disappears through a secret passage behind a velvet curtain just before the mob arrives. Upon entering, Meg finds only the Phantom's white mask.
Moving back to 1919, the elderly Raoul visits Christine's gravesite and places the music box near her tombstone. He stands in silence for a moment and then turns to leave, but stops upon noticing a fresh red rose with a black ribbon tied around the stem with Christine's engagement ring attached to it; implying that the Phantom is alive, and still loves Christine.</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id" boost="1.0">4</field>
		<field name="release" boost="1.0">2001</field>
		<field name="title" boost="4.0">In the Bedroom</field>
		<field name="origin" boost="1.0">American</field>
		<field name="director" boost="1.0">Todd Field</field>
		<field name="cast" boost="1.0">Tom Wilkinson, Sissy Spacek, Nick Stahl, Marisa Tomei</field>
		<field name="genre" boost="1.0">crime drama</field>
		<field name="wikipage" boost="1.0">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/In_the_Bedroom</field>
		<field name="plot" boost="2.0">The film is set in the Mid-Coast town of Camden, Maine. Matt (Tom Wilkinson) and Ruth Fowler (Sissy Spacek) enjoy a happy marriage and a good relationship with their son Frank (Nick Stahl), a recent college graduate who has come home for the summer. Frank has fallen in love with an older woman with children, Natalie Strout (Marisa Tomei).
Frank is about to begin post graduate school for architecture, but is having second thoughts and considering staying in town to continue working as a fisherman and, more important, to be near Natalie. Natalie's ex-husband, Richard Strout (William Mapother), tries to find a way into his ex-wife and children's lives, going to increasingly violent lengths to get his intentions across to Natalie. Ruth is openly concerned about Frank's relationship with Natalie, while Matt thinks it is only a fling.
Midway through the film, Richard kills Frank during a confrontation at Natalie's house following a domestic dispute. Though equally devastated, Matt and Ruth grieve in different ways, with Matt putting on a brave face while Ruth becomes reclusive and quiet. Richard is set free on bail, paid by his well-to-do family, and both Matt and Ruth are forced to see Richard around town.
The tension between Matt and Ruth increases when they learn that the lack of an eyewitness to Frank's shooting means Richard will instead be charged with accidental manslaughter. An argument erupts between the couple in which each one confronts the other. With the air cleared, the couple is finally able to find common ground in their grief.
Matt then abducts and kills Richard. He and a friend bury the body on the friend's wooded property. Matt returns home to Ruth, who is awake and smoking in bed. She asks him, "Did you do it?" Matt appears troubled and unresponsive. He climbs into bed and then turns away from her. Finally, Ruth gets up to make coffee. Matt rolls over onto his back and pulls a band-aid from a finger he injured hauling traps. Ruth calls from the kitchen, "Matt, do you want coffee?" Matt doesn't answer.</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id" boost="1.0">5</field>
		<field name="release" boost="1.0">2005</field>
		<field name="title" boost="4.0">The Piano Tuner of Earthquakes</field>
		<field name="origin" boost="1.0">British</field>
		<field name="director" boost="1.0">Stephen Quay, Timothy Quay</field>
		<field name="cast" boost="1.0">Amira Casar, Gottfried John, Assumpta Serna</field>
		<field name="genre" boost="1.0">fantasy</field>
		<field name="wikipage" boost="1.0">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Piano_Tuner_of_Earthquakes</field>
		<field name="plot" boost="2.0">A 19th-century opera singer is murdered on-stage shortly before her forthcoming wedding. Soon after being slain by the nefarious Dr. Emmanuel Droz during a live performance, Malvina van Stille is spirited away to the inventor's remote villa to be reanimated and forced to play the lead in a grim production staged to recreate her abduction. As the time for the performance draws near, piano tuner of earthquakes Felisberto sets out to activate the seven essential automata who dot the dreaded doctor's landscape and make sure all the essential elements are in place. Once again instilled with life after her brief stay in the afterworld, amnesiac Malvina is soon drawn to the mysterious Felisberto as a result of his uncanny resemblance to her one-time fiancé Adolfo.</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id" boost="1.0">6</field>
		<field name="release" boost="1.0">2013</field>
		<field name="title" boost="4.0">All in All Azhagu Raja</field>
		<field name="origin" boost="1.0">Tamil</field>
		<field name="director" boost="1.0">M. Rajesh</field>
		<field name="cast" boost="1.0">Karthi, Kajal Aggarwal, Santhanam</field>
		<field name="genre" boost="1.0">comedy</field>
		<field name="wikipage" boost="1.0">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/All_in_All_Azhagu_Raja</field>
		<field name="plot" boost="2.0">Azhagu Raja (Karthi), is the only son of the Muthukrishnan family. He owns an unpopular cable channel called "Triple A". The cable company has only two employees, Raja and Kalyanam (Santhanam). Nothing they do improves the company's fortunes. By chance, Raja meets Devi Priya (Kajal Aggarwal) when she is singing at a wedding. Her unusual voice irritates him and they argue. However, Priya eventually agrees that she cannot sing well. Priya says she fails at everything she tries, even suicide. As their friendship blossoms, Raja tells his father, Muthukrishnan, about Priya which triggers a memory in Muthukrishnan about his past.
He used to work for Burma Ramaswamy (Nassar) after being recommended by Kali (Santhanam), Seeing his hard work &amp; dedication, Burma Ramaswamy promotes him to more responsible work in the theatre and appoints Kali under him. An enraged Kali,filled with jealousy plots to pit Burma Ramaswamy against Muthukrishnan &amp; is successful when Muthukrishnan is ousted by Ramaswamy due to a misunderstanding.
Raja steps into Muthukrishnan's 1980s world. Muthukrishnan and Priya's father, Kandhaswamy reject Raja's marriage to Priya. Muthukrishnan and Kandhaswamy meet &amp; realise that jealousy of Kali, Kalyanam's father was the reason for the problems of the families; finally Kalyanam tells the real story &amp; both families unite to marry Raja and Priya .[4]</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id" boost="1.0">7</field>
		<field name="release" boost="1.0">2002</field>
		<field name="title" boost="4.0">Igby Goes Down</field>
		<field name="origin" boost="1.0">American</field>
		<field name="director" boost="1.0">Burr Steers</field>
		<field name="cast" boost="1.0">Kieran Culkin, Claire Danes, Jeff Goldblum, Susan Sarandon</field>
		<field name="genre" boost="1.0">comedy, drama</field>
		<field name="wikipage" boost="1.0">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Igby_Goes_Down</field>
		<field name="plot" boost="2.0">Jason "Igby" Slocumb, Jr. (Kieran Culkin) is a misanthropic 17-year-old boy, rebelling against the oppressive world of his strict East Coast "old money" family. His schizophrenic father, Jason (Bill Pullman), has been committed to an institution. Igby fears he will eventually suffer a mental breakdown like his father. His mother, Mimi (Susan Sarandon), is self-absorbed and distant and has a tendency to drink heavily. Igby mockingly describes his ambitious older brother Ollie (Ryan Phillippe) as a fascist or, alternatively, a Young Republican, and that he studies "neo-fascism" (economics) at Columbia University.
Igby figures there must be a better life out there, and he sets out to find it, rebelling against his family at every opportunity. After happily flunking out of several prep schools, he ends up in a brutal military academy where he gets beaten by his classmates. After escaping and spending time in a Chicago hotel courtesy of his mother's credit card, Igby is sent to New York for the summer to his godfather D.H. Banes (Jeff Goldblum).
While working construction for D.H., Igby first encounters Rachel (Amanda Peet), his godfather's heroin-addicted trophy mistress. Rather than return to school, he escapes into the bohemian underworld of Manhattan, hiding out with Rachel and her performance artist friend Russel (Jared Harris). Eventually, he and Rachel have sex. After being suspected and scolded by D.H., he then hooks up with terminally bored, part-time lover, Sookie (Claire Danes), only for her to later leave him for Ollie.
Despite seeming cold and distant, Mimi is not unaffected by her rebellious son. She describes Igby's conception as an act of animosity and it shouldn't be a surprise that his life follows the same course. His name is explained as a family in-joke. As a child, he would blame his toy bear, Digby, for things he had done, mispronouncing it as "Igby". In order to get him to take responsibility for his actions, his family would call him Igby whenever he lied.
Igby is informed by Russell that his mother Mimi is dying from breast cancer and so he returns to see her. She has arranged to commit suicide with help from Ollie, who feeds her poisoned strawberry yogurt.
Before she dies, Mimi makes a final revelation, casually inquiring of Igby, "I take it you know that D.H. is your father?" Igby leaves for Los Angeles in an attempt to finally make a clean break by getting 3,000 miles away from his family.</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id" boost="1.0">8</field>
		<field name="release" boost="1.0">2009</field>
		<field name="title" boost="4.0">Evaraina Epudaina</field>
		<field name="origin" boost="1.0">Telugu</field>
		<field name="director" boost="1.0">Marthand K. Shankar</field>
		<field name="cast" boost="1.0">Varun Sandesh, Vimala Raman</field>
		<field name="genre" boost="1.0">romance</field>
		<field name="wikipage" boost="1.0">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Evaraina_Epudaina</field>
		<field name="plot" boost="2.0">Venkat (Varun Sandesh) is a carefree guy. He is a smart youngster who looks for people around him who are in love, then he blackmails them by threatening to tell their family of their love unless they pay him money for his silence. He gets into a fight because he took money from a couple by blackmailing, there he sees a girl Madhumita (Vimala Raman) and it is love at first sight for Venkat. Meanwhile, his grandma gets hurt and he takes her to a hospital, an old woman is admitted in the same room, later he finds out she is Madhumita's grandma (Rama Prabha). He gets an opportunity to impress her, he pretends to save her grandma and they both become good friends. Venkat's close friend (Adarsh) confesses him that he is in love with the daughter of Madhumita's father (Giri Babu). He thinks that his friend is going to be engaged to Madhumita.
This prompts Venkat to play a spoilsport during the engagement ceremony, he tries to break the engagement and also succeeds in breaking the engagement. Soon after the engagement breaks he realised that his friend is in love with Madhumita's sister and was getting engaged to her. Venkat is shocked and is in a fixed situation as he can't tell the truth to Madhumita and her family as they would hate him after knowing the truth. He gets close to her family in the meantime, also Madhumita falls in love with him. In the temple, she overhears Venkat's friend telling him that it was a good plan to break Adarsh and Madumita's sister's engagement. Venkat sees Madhumita and tries to explain to her that it was an misunderstanding but she was not ready to listen. Venkat then become a responsible person and joins his brother's office, he respects lovers and understands other's feeling. He also manages to get Adarsh and Madhumita's sister together in the meantime. He then goes to Madhumita and explains to her and tries to convince her that everything was a misunderstanding, he tells her that he is a changed person and has got a good job for her. She understands him and his feeling's, the film ends with Venkat and Madhumita getting together.</field>
	</doc>
	<doc>
		<field name="id" boost="1.0">9</field>
		<field name="release" boost="1.0">2002</field>
		<field name="title" boost="4.0">23rd March 1931: Shaheed</field>
		<field name="origin" boost="1.0">Bollywood</field>
		<field name="director" boost="1.0">Guddu Dhanoa</field>
		<field name="cast" boost="1.0">Sunny Deol, Bobby Deol, Divya Dutta, Aishwarya Rai, Amrita Singh</field>
		<field name="genre" boost="1.0">historical drama</field>
		<field name="wikipage" boost="1.0">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/23rd_March_1931:_Shaheed</field>
		<field name="plot" boost="2.0">Set in 1931, British India, the film tells the story of freedom fighters Bhagat Singh and Chandrashekhar Azad who have only one motive in mind: Freedom for India. They set about doing this task together with two other men, Sukhdev and Rajguru. Bhagat Singh is enraged when his mentor Lala Lajpatrai is mercilessly beaten to death by the police, and he sets about to avenge his death. He and his colleagues do succeed in killing one of the officials responsible, but they are identified and as a result Bhagat and Rajguru are arrested and held in prison where they are tortured relentlessly.
When produced in court, they dramatically admit to the killing and claim that it was done in the name of Freedom. The judge and the public prosecutor do not see it that their way and they are sentenced to life in prison. Bhagat's mother, Vidya, comes to meet him in prison, and he goes to greet her, shackled in chains from head to toe, and he foretells that India will continue to suffer, even after Independence from the British, and that he will return in another birth to free his motherland. Subsequently, all three are charged with treason and assassination and are sentenced to death.</field>
	</doc>
</add>